

# Damy op den Kamp

### **Gameplay Programmer**

Phone: +3| 6|84959|8

© E-Mail: d.opdkamp@gmail.com

Portfolio: <a href="https://www.damyodk.com">https://www.damyodk.com</a>

Addres
Breda, The Netherlands

My name is Damy and I'm a game developer from the Netherlands. I have a passion for creating experiences and have been doing so for over 10 years with mainly experience in modding games.

Now studying technical game design with an already obtained programming degree developing my creative skills even further.

## **Work Experience**

July 2022 - September 2022

## Game Developer at Diamond Studios, Remote

As game developer for Diamond Studios I worked on creating modded Minecraft experiences for a wide audience.

September 2022 - January 2023

## Gameplay & Tool Programmer at Team Workbench, Amsterdam On-Site

As gameplay and tool programmer for Team Workbench I worked on in-house tools to improve our workflows and worked on modded Minecraft educational experiences

#### **Education**

September 2018 - July 2022

Software Development at ROC Nijmegen In this 4 year course I learned the ropes of programming. While I already had experience with programming I learned a lot about web development and scrum here.

September 2023 - Current

# Creative Media & Game Technologies at Breda University of Applied Sciences

In my first year followed the programming course and switched to Technical Design in my second year to improve my skills in the area of design. This course aligns more with what I want to do in the future.

#### **Hobbies**

Hiking, Improv, Music and I love cooking,



#### **S**kills

Unreal Engine, C++, Technical Game Design Git, Perforce, Steamworks C#, Java, Web Development